http://www.newdream.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
New Dream is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our site, the members of our Community and donors to the Project. New Dream is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.
Typical of most websites, New Dream collects information from visitors at several different points on this website: the name of your Internet service provider, the browser and type of machine you are using, the website that referred you to us, the pages you request and the date and time you request them. The information we collect is used to improve the content and utility of our website for visitors. This information is not shared with any other organizations for commercial purposes.
In order to participate in some activities, you might be asked to provide some personal information, such as your name, email address, mailing address, or phone number. We request this information, on an opt-in basis, to join our Community or download our resources, for instance. We do not collect personal information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis. You may unsubscribe from our e-mail list at any time by contacting newdream@newdream.org.
To process a charitable contribution, service, or product purchase, it is necessary for New Dream to gather the visitor’s name, email address, mailing address, phone, and credit card information. This data is used to verify identity and execute the financial transaction. Additionally, phone number and email address information may be used to contact visitors if there is a problem with the transaction.
New Dream may use service providers (such as merchant banks and ecommerce integrators) for the express purpose of conducting financial transactions. Personal information is kept private and secure and is not sold, rented, or traded to third parties. It is important to note that credit card numbers are used only at the time of the transaction, and are not stored following the conclusion of the transaction unless a transaction is selected that occurs on a regular basis. For transactions that recur, credit card information is stored in an encrypted format.
Our site may contain links to other sites that are not managed or maintained by New Dream. The inclusion of a link to another site does not imply any endorsement of that site’s privacy policies, practices, or content. Your dealings with these sites are covered only by the privacy policies listed on those sites.
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, membership in our Community, or a contribution, please contact us at newdream@newdream.org.
